

Ravi Shekhar Frontend Developer

About

Hello there! My name is **Ravi Shekhar**. I am a frontend developer based in Bihar, India. I am self-motivated and self-learner. I am very passionate and dedicated to my work.

I have over 14 years of experience in Drupal / WordPress theme development and website management. I have also contributed few Drupal 7/8/9 themes at drupal.org

Name: Ravi Shekhar Address: Darbhanga, Bihar, India

Birthday: 08 oct, 1984 Nationality: Indian

Languages: Hindi and English Freelance: Available

Resume

#Education

2004-2008

B.E (Electronics & Communication)

I.E.T, Dr. B.R Ambedkar University, Agra, UP, India

2011-2013

M.B.A (Marketing)

L.N.M university

Darbhanga, Bihar, India

#Experience

2012-current

Drupar.com

Drupal theme developer.

2014-current

Dewdot.com

Website development and maintenance.

2009-current

YagHost.com

Server management.

#Technical Skills

HTML

CSS: CSS3, SASS

JavaScript

jQuery

Reactjs, Nextjs

PHP (intermediate)

WordPress Theme Development

Drupal theme development

Framework: Bootstrap, Bulma

Version Control System: Git

IDE: VScode, Atom, Notepad++

Operating System: Windows 10

Multimedia Tools: Figma

Systems Administration: FTP, SSH, cPanel. DirectAdmin

•

Domain: DNS management

Others: SEO, Google Page Speed Optimization

Blog

I love blogging related to web development and web hosting. Please check my blogs.

- //dewcodes.com
- //dewcodes.com//lophost.com

Social Profiles

GitHub: //github.com/dewdot

Drupal: //drupal.org/u/ravis

in Linkedin: //linkedin.com/in/ravi3

Contact



Call Me

+91 - 9122574715



Mail Me ravi9793@gmail.com



Address

New sagar colony, Darbhanga, Bihar, India